Guide to the Clesson Nathan Turner papers, [ca. 1926]-1987.
Turner, Clesson Nathan papers, [ca. 1926]-1987.
- Building Farm Load - Proposed Farm Service Program (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Untitled (Box 12, Folder 11)
- County Agent Poultry Training School, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- New York Farm Electrification Council (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Practical Farm Wiring Demonstrations, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Residential Electric Water Heater Study - By N.A. Tudi, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Electric Water Heater Performance for Dairy Farms --By N.A. Tudi & C.N. Turner, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- A Shallow Well Water System (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Leader's Manual for Demonstration and Lessons in Planning Farm Wiring Systems (Box 12, Folder 18)
- A Report on the State Wide Survey of Rural Electric Lines in Representative Parts of the State of Washington (Box 12, Folder 19)
- A Progress Report of Investigation by the Washington Committee on the Relation of Electricity to Agriculture, 1929 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- A Progress Report of Investigations of the Various uses of Electricity on the Farms of Washington, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- A Progress Report of Investigations of the Various uses of Electricity on the Farms of Washington, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- A Progress Report of Investigations of the Various uses of Electricity on the Farms of Washington, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- A Progress Report of Investigations of the Various uses of Electricity on the Farms of Washington, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Electricity on Farms in Eastern Washington (Box 12, Folder 25)
- General Electric Company - Summary of the New York Project, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Electricity on the Farm and In Rural Communities (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Preliminary Report on Farm Electrification Research, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Ninth Annual Report to the Committee on the Relation of Electricity to Agriculture by the Director, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Tenth Annual Report to the Committee on the Relation of Electricity to Agriculture by the Director, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Thirteenth Annual Report to the Committee on the Relation of Electricity to Agriculture by the Director, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Progress Report on Standard Dimensions for Concrete Milk Cooling Tank, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Loose Papers (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Cooperative Electric Brooder Project (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Loose Papers (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Agricultural Engineering, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Agricultural Engineering, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Agricultural Engineering, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Agricultural Engineering, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Agricultural Engineering, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 40)